George Gaylord Simpson Papers 1918-1984 Mss.Ms.Coll.31
American Philosophical Society
- George Gaylord Simpson Papers
  - Series I. Correspondence, 1925-1984; 36 linear feet (Box 1-73)
    - Holiday Inn (Tallahessee, Florida), 1973 (Box 30)
    - Hollaender, Alexander, 1959 (Box 30)
    - Holland, George P., 1951, 62, 69 (Box 30)
    - Holland, James G., 1947, 50, 54, 67 (Box 30)
    - Holland, William J. (W.J.), 1926-27, 29 (Box 30)
    - Holman, J. Alan, 1968 (Box 30)
    - Holmes, DeField T., 1961 (Box 30)
    - Holmes, Walter W., 1928-29, 30-35, 37 (Box 30)
      Florida land mammals manuscript
    - Holroyd, Howard B., 1972 (Box 30)
    - Holt, Ernest G., 1941 (Box 30)
    - Holt, Rinehart, and Winston, Inc., 1959-60, 64-66, 72 (Box 30)
    - Holton, Charlotte, 1963, 71 (Box 30)
    - Holtzman, Richard C., 1975, 79 (Box 30)
    - Holum, John R., 1964-65 (Box 30)
    - Honey, James G., 1978, 81 (Box 30)
    - Honigmann, Hans Leo., 1931 (Box 30)
    - Honkavaara, Sylvia, 1966 (Box 30)
    - Hood, Elizabeth M., 1973 (Box 30)
    - Hood, J. Douglas, 1953 (Box 30)
    - Hooijer, Dirk A. (Dirk Albert), 1948-1981; 40.0 Item(s) (Box 30)
      Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia; Educational matters; Educational matters -- Netherlands; Evolution -- Teeth; Leakey, Louis Seymour Bazett; Paleontology; Publication; Requests for aid in finding positions; Requests for reprints; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Teilhard de Chardin, Pierre; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Wood, Horace; Zoology
    - Hooper, E.T., 1937 (Box 30)
    - Hooper, Emmet T., 1937, 46 (Box 30)
    - Hoots, Harold W., 1960 (Box 30)
    - Hoover, W. Scott, 1975 (Box 30)
    - Hope, Chester, 1949 (Box 30)
    - Hopf, Alice L., 1977 (Box 30)
    - Hopkins, Jeannette, 1971-72 (Box 30)
      Harcourt, Brace, and World
    - Hopkins, Jerry W., 1969 (Box 30)
    - Hopkins, Sewell Hopborn, 1983 (Box 30)
    - Hopla, Cluff E., 1964 (Box 30)
    - Hopson, James A., 1972, 77-78, 82-83 (Box 30)
    - Hopwood, Arthur Tindle, 1927-1960; 49.0 Item(s) (Box 30)
      Biographical and personal data; British Museum; Displaced German scholars; Evolution; Evolution -- Teeth; Leakey, Louis Seymour Bazett; Osborn, Henry Fairfield; Paleontology; Political issues; Publication; Travel -- France; Travel -- India; World War II -- England; Zoology
    - Horizon, 1966 (Box 30)
    - Hormann, Klaus, 1961 (Box 30)
    - Horn and Wallace, 1965 (Box 30)
    - Horn, Michael H., 1971 (Box 30)
    - Horner, P.F., 1965 (Box 30)
    - Horse and Mule Association of America, 1948, 53 (Box 30)
    - Hoshaw, Robert W., 1960 (Box 30)
    - Hoslett, Sherman A., 1933 (Box 30)
    - Hospital of Saint Barnabas, 1953 (Box 30)
    - Hotton, Nicholas III, 1967 (Box 30)
    - Houck, Margaret E., 1948 (Box 30)
    - Hough, Jean, 1947, 54-57 (Box 30)
    - Hougland, Willard, 1948 (Box 30)
    - House, M.R., 1979 (Box 30)
    - Houston, R.S., 1971 (Box 30)
    - Houton, Franklyn B. van, 1940 (Box 30)
    - Hoveland, Niemen, 1940 (Box 30)
    - Howard, Hildegarde, 1947, 57, 80 (Box 30)
    - Howard, John K., 1935 (Box 30)
    - Howard, Warren R., 1966 (Box 30)
    - Howe, Ernest, 1926-28 (Box 30)
      American Journal of Science
    - Howell, A. Brazier, 1932, 37-39 (Box 31)
    - Howell, Arthur H., 1940 (Box 31)
    - Howell, B.F., 1932-33, 35, 47 (Box 31)
    - Howell, F. CLark, 1959-60, 67 (Box 31)
    - Howell, Thomas R., 1969 (Box 31)
    - Howells, Thomas H., 1963 (Box 31)
    - Howells, William W., 1949-65 (Box 31)
    - Howie, Anne, 1969 (Box 31)
    - Hoyt, Elizabeth E., 1967, 69-70 (Box 31)
    - Hoyt, Willard J., 1964 (Box 31)
      Eugenics
    - Hu, Chang-kang, 1980 (Box 31)
    - Hubbard Scientific Co., 1967 (Box 31)
    - Hubbard, Andy, 1968 (Box 31)
    - Hubbard, Geo. D., 1942 (Box 31)
    - Hubbs, Carl L., 1944-46, 56 (Box 31)
    - Hubel, Gordon, 1962 (Box 31)
    - Huddle, J.W., 1937 (Box 31)
    - Hudson, Nancy, 1935 (Box 31)
    - Huene, Erika Von, 1926-28, 32, 34-35, 50 (Box 31)
      The bulk of this folder contains correspondence from Erika von Huene's father, Friedrich von Huene.
    - Huffman, Edward W., 1961 (Box 31)
    - Hughes, Everett C., 1966 (Box 31)
    - Hughes, Stanley A., Jr., 1964 (Box 31)
    - Hughes-Schrader, Sally, 1964 (Box 31)
    - Huheey, James E., 1964 (Box 31)
      The Plain Truth
    - Huler, Lewis, 1973 (Box 31)
    - Hull, David Lee, 1963, 65, 77-78 (Box 31)
    - Human Genetics Society, n.d. (Box 31)
    - Humanities Center for Liberal Education, 1958 (Box 31)
    - Hume, C.W., 1959 (Box 31)
      vivisection
    - Hume, G.S., 1941 (Box 31)
    - Humman, William D., 1966 (Box 31)
    - Humphrey, Donald G., 1963, 69 (Box 31)
    - Humphrey, Louise, 1960 (Box 31)
    - Hunicken, Mario, 1982 (Box 31)
    - Hunt, Charles B., 1965 (Box 31)
    - Hunt, George L., 1974 (Box 31)
    - Hunt, Robert, Jr., 1980 (Box 31)
    - Hunter College of the City of New York, 1928, 52 (Box 31)
    - Hunter, Fenley, 1932-39, 41 (Box 31)
    - Huntington, E. Irving, 1942 (Box 31)
    - Huntington, Henry S., 1962-63 (Box 31)
      Survivorship measures and selection
    - Huntsman, A.G., 1963 (Box 31)
    - Hunziker, Juan H., 1976 (Box 31)
    - Hurst, C.T., 1941 (Box 31)
    - Hurtubia, Jaime, 1970 (Box 31)
    - Hurzeler, Johannes, 1937, 58, 68 (Box 31)
    - Husband, Rachel Alice, 1933-34 (Box 31)
      Also under Nichols, Rachel Husband
    - Hussakof, Louis, 1932 (Box 31)
    - Hutton, William L., 1937 (Box 31)
    - Huxley, Julian, 1938-1974; 3 folders (Box 31)
      Behavioral genetics, IQ; Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia -- Darwin Centennial; Evolution; Evolution -- Horses; Genetics Society of America -- Golden Jubilee; Human genetics; Leakey, Louis Seymour Bazett; Lectures, public speaking; Mayr, Ernst; Paleontology; Poetry and literature; Population, demography; Publication -- Quantitative Zoology; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs -- Zoological Society of London; Travel -- Antarctica; Travel -- South America; Zoology; Zoology -- Classification
    - Huxley, Juliette (Lady) and Sir Andrew, 1975, 81-83 (Box 31)
      Memorial fund
    - Hyman, Chester, 1963 (Box 31)
    - Iberall, Arthur S., 1975 (Box 31)
    - Idaho State University, 1969 (Box 31)
    - Ierardi, Tom, 1947 (Box 31)
    - Iglesias, Dolores, 1943 (Box 31)
    - Iino, Catherine, 1979 (Box 31)
      American Scientist
    - Iliff, Warren J., 1977 (Box 31)
    - Illinois Science Lecture Association, 1975 (Box 31)
    - Illinois, State Geological Survey of, 1955 (Box 31)
    - Illinois, University of (Urbana), 1950, 55 (Box 31)
      lecture
    - Imbrie, John, 1961, 63, 70 (Box 32)
    - Immergut, Edmund H., 1978-80 (Box 32)
      Fossils
    - Imperial Chemical Industries, Ltd., 1946 (Box 32)
    - Imsland, Donald O., 1971 (Box 32)
    - Income Tax Bureau (State of New York), 1947 (Box 32)
    - Ingle, Dwight J., 1962, 70-73, 77 (Box 32)
    - Ingram, Edward G., 1959 (Box 32)
    - Ingram, George, 1931 (Box 32)
    - Ingram, Rupert H., 1962 (Box 32)
      McGraw Hill Co.
    - Ingram, William M., 1943 (Box 32)
    - Innes Publishing Company, 1933 (Box 32)
    - Institute for Muscle Research, 1949 (Box 32)
    - Institute for Scientific Information, 1983-84 (Box 32)
    - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, 1966 (Box 32)
    - Institute on Religion in an Age of Science, 1956 (Box 32)
      Conference
    - Instituto Nacional De Antropologia E. Historia, 1969 (Box 32)
    - Instituto Nacional De Investigacion de las Ciencias Naturales, 1959 (Box 32)
    - Instituto Provinvial de Paleontologia, 1975 (Box 32)
    - Interior, United States Department of the, 1938 (Box 32)
      Bill before Congress
    - International Chronosophial Society, 1965 (Box 32)
    - International Commission on Zoological Nomenclature, 1950, 56, 62-71, 74-75 (Box 32)
    - International Conference on the Unity of Science, 5th annual, 1976 (Box 32)
    - International Congress of Zoology, 1935, 56-58, 62 (Box 32)
    - International Education Board, 1926-27, 29 (Box 32)
    - International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, 1964 (Box 32)
    - International Geological Congress, 7th session, 1935-37 (Box 32)
    - International Paleontological Union, 1968 (Box 32)
    - International Primatological Society, 1965 (Box 32)
    - International Scientific and Technological Affairs (United States Department of State), 1969 (Box 32)
    - International Society for the Study of Time, 1966 (Box 32)
    - International Theriological Congress, 1973-74, 81, 83-84 (Box 32)
    - International Union of Biological Sciences, 1949 (Box 32)
    - Iowa State Teachers College, 1955 (Box 32)
    - Irvine, William, 1955 (Box 32)
      Darwin and chronic illness as brucellosis
    - Irving, George W., 1963 (Box 32)
    - Irwin, John, 1982 (Box 32)
    - Irwin, Joseph S., 1965 (Box 32)
    - Isaacson, Peter E., 1975 (Box 32)
    - Isbell, Horace, 1963 (Box 32)
    - Isis (journal), 1965-66 (Box 32)
    - Istituto della Enciclopedia Italiana, 1972 (Box 32)
    - Itineraries, 1964 (Box 32)
    - Ivy, A.C., 1935-37 (Box 32)
    - Jackson, Donald D., 1958 (Box 32)
      Univ. of Illinois Press
    - Jackson, Harry Frederick, 1960 (Box 32)
    - Jackson, Miles, 1984 (Box 32)
    - Jackson, S. Wesley, 1970 (Box 32)
    - Jacobowitz, Ira, 1961 (Box 32)
    - Jacobs, Louis, 1977-82, 84 (Box 32)
    - Jacobson, David M., 1971 (Box 32)
    - Jadot, Alice, 1936 (Box 32)
      Reading list in paleontology
    - Jaeger, Edmund C., 1941 (Box 32)
    - Jaffe, Edward, 1960 (Box 32)
    - Jaffe, Marc, 1958 (Box 32)
    - Jagannath, R.S., 1982 (Box 32)
    - Jagow, E.C., 1963 (Box 32)
    - Jahn, Alfredo, 1939 (Box 32)
    - Jahn, Melvin E., 1960 (Box 32)
    - Jahn, T.H., 1953 (Box 32)
    - James, Edward T., 1971 (Box 32)
    - James, Gideon T., 1961 (Box 32)
    - James, Gladden Wm., 1952 (Box 32)
    - James, H. Brooks, 1963 (Box 32)
    - James, Harold L., 1971 (Box 32)
    - James, W. Warwick, 1962 (Box 32)
    - Janensch, W., 1936 (Box 33)
    - Janis, Christine, 1979 (Box 33)
    - Janke, Carl, 1968 (Box 33)
    - Janney, Russell, 1934 (Box 33)
    - Janvier, Philippe, 1981, 83 (Box 33)
    - Janzen, Daniel H., 1980 (Box 33)
    - Jaques, H.E., 1954 (Box 33)
    - Jarrett, Guy, 1957 (Box 33)
    - Jastrow, Robert, 1967, 72-73 (Box 33)
    - Jay, Phyllis, 1968 (Box 33)
    - Jeffreys, Harold, 1958, 65, 80, 84 (Box 33)
    - Jeletzky, J.A., 1961 (Box 33)
    - Jellinek, E. Morton, 1937, 42-43 (Box 33)
    - Jellison, William L., 1946 (Box 33)
    - Jenkins, D. Graham, 1960 (Box 33)
    - Jenkins, Farish A., Jr., 1965, 68, 73-75, 78-80 (Box 33)
    - Jenkins, Richard J.F., 1975-76 (Box 33)
    - Jenney, C.E., 1940 (Box 33)
      Travel on Canadian railroads
    - Jennings, Jesse D., 1965 (Box 33)
    - Jensen, Henry W., 1966 (Box 33)
    - Jensen, James A., 1964, 69, 79-81 (Box 33)
    - Jenssen, Denis, 1964 (Box 33)
    - Jentys-Szaferowa, J., 1965 (Box 33)
    - Jepsen, Glenn Lowell, 1929-32, 34-42, 44-60, 62, 64 (Box 33)
    - Jepson, Susan B., 1981 (Box 33)
      Systematics Association
    - Jerison, Harry J., 1960, 68, 71-74, 80-81 (Box 33)
      Critique of Evol of Brain and Behavior manuscript
    - Jesmok, Gary, 1968 (Box 33)
    - Jex, Hope Satterthwaite (Mrs. John), 1953 (Box 33)
    - Jockey Club, The, 1948 (Box 33)
    - Johanne, Robert, 1965 (Box 33)
    - Johannessen, Carl L., 1973 (Box 33)
    - Johnson Reprint Co., 1972 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, Cecil E., 1966 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, Donald Lee, 1970, 75 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, Douglas, 1941 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, F. Walker, 1936 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, L.A.S., 1969 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, Peter, 1972, 74 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, Ralph G., 1975 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, Ralph M., 1972 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, Robert K., 1967-70 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, Ross, 1954 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, Shirley A., 1967 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, Verne L., 1977 (Box 33)
    - Johnson, Walter J., Inc., 1953-54 (Box 33)
      Sell periodicals
    - Johnson, Willis H., 1955, 66 (Box 33)
      diagram of horse evolution
    - Johnston, Bernard, 1975 (Box 33)
      Great Soviet Encyclopedia
    - Johnston, H.F., 1947 (Box 33)
    - Johnston, Richard F., 1969, 82-84 (Box 33)
      Annual Review of Ecology and Systematics
    - Jolicoeur, Pierre, 1966 (Box 33)
    - Jones, Arthur W., 1960 (Box 33)
      Should we teach human evolution?
    - Jones, J. Knox, Jr., 1968, 73 (Box 33)
    - Jones, Janet M., 1976 (Box 33)
    - Jones, John H., 1965-67 (Box 33)
      Jones Trust and GGS beneficiary
    - Jones, Louis C., 1944 (Box 33)
    - Jones, Marshall R., 1958 (Box 33)
    - Journal of Mammology, 1962, 75 (Box 33)
    - Journal of Paleontology, 1942, 44, 47, 49-50, 55, 71, 74, 80 (Box 33)
      Referee
    - Journal of the History of the Behavioral Sciences, 1965 (Box 33)
    - Jouventin, Pierre, 1978, 80, 82 (Box 33)
    - Jovanovich, William, 1966, 69 (Box 33)
    - Jovitis, Peter, 1962 (Box 33)
    - Jukes, Thomas H., 1969, 75 (Box 33)
    - Jules Chain Stores Corporation, 1939 (Box 33)
    - Junk, W., 1927-31, 75 (Box 33)
    - Just, Theodor, 1945, 47, 59 (Box 33)
    - Justo, Enrique Roberto, 1980 (Box 33)
    - Justus, Philip, 1960 (Box 33)
    - Jutson, J. T., 1943 (Box 33)
    - Kaellis, Eugene, 1963 (Box 34)
    - Kahn Foundation for the Foreign Travel of American Teachers, 1926 (Box 34)
    - Kahn, Theodore C., 1966 (Box 34)
    - Kaiser, H.E., 1970 (Box 34)
    - Kalin, Prof., 1966 (Box 34)
    - Kamen-Kaye, Maurice (Mrs.) (Dorothy), 1966, 71, 73-80 (Box 34)
    - Kansas, University of, 1958, 62, 66 (Box 34)
    - Kantor, Mackinlay, 1960 (Box 34)
    - Kao, Jen Way, 1976 (Box 34)
    - Karabin, Nicholas, Jr., 1981 (Box 34)
    - Kardong, Kenneth V., 1979 (Box 34)
    - Karplus, Robert, 1962 (Box 34)
    - Karrer, S., 1964 (Box 34)
    - Katsh, Deborah, 1980 (Box 34)
    - Katt, Rhoda Steel, 1960 (Box 34)
    - Katz, Michael J., 1978 (Box 34)
    - Kaufman Company, 1938 (Box 34)
    - Kaunitz, Hans, 1963 (Box 34)
    - Kay, J. LeRoy, 1936-42, 47, 57 (Box 34)
    - Kay, Richard F., 1983 (Box 34)
    - Keast, Allen, 1962-63, 65, 67, 71 (Box 34)
    - Keath, Charles Ltd., 1979 (Box 34)
    - Keay, R.W.J., 1970 (Box 34)
    - Keeler, Carl R., 1957 (Box 34)
    - Keenan, Philip, 1940 (Box 34)
    - Keeping, Pat, 1960 (Box 34)
    - Kegan, Paul, Trench, Trubner, and Co., Ltd., 1943 (Box 34)
    - Keith, Linton J., 1960 (Box 34)
    - Keller, Gloria B., 1977 (Box 34)
    - Kellogg, H. Dudley, 1977 (Box 34)
    - Kellogg, John P., 1925 (Box 34)
    - Kellogg, Remington, 1926, 32-35, 37-39, 80 (Box 34)
    - Kellum, Lewis B., 1946 (Box 34)
    - Kelly, Catharine Howe, 1960 (Box 34)
      UPI, Jesup Lesctures
    - Kelly, Harry C., 1962 (Box 34)
      NSF
    - Kelly, Michael, 1965 (Box 34)
    - Kempf, Walter W., 1963 (Box 34)
    - Kendall, Janet, 1969 (Box 34)
    - Kendall/Hunt Publishing Co., 1974 (Box 34)
    - Kenna, Margaret E., 1975 (Box 34)
    - Kennedy, George A., 1936, 69 (Box 34)
    - Kennedy, Manert H., 1975 (Box 34)
      BSCS
    - Kennedy, W.J., 1975 (Box 34)
    - Kenyon College, 1968 (Box 34)
    - Keosian, John, 1962 (Box 34)
    - Kepes, Gyorgy, 1961-62 (Box 34)
    - Kermack, Kenneth A. and Doris M., 1958, 65, 67-70, 72-73, 75-81, 83 (Box 34)
    - Kerr, Chester, 1973, 75, 78-79 (Box 34)
    - Kerr, Paul F., 1938-39 (Box 34)
    - Kesling, Robert V., 1960 (Box 34)
    - Keystone News and Photo Service, 1932 (Box 34)
    - Khajuria, H., 1962, 69, 71-72 (Box 34)
    - Khan, Ehsanullah, 1956, 61 (Box 34)
    - Khare, Sushil Kumar, 1972 (Box 34)
    - Kidr, Johan, 1926 (Box 34)
    - Kielan-Jaworowska, Zofia, 1970-73, 76, 82 (Box 34)
    - Kier, Porter M., 1973, 76 (Box 34)
    - Kiester, A. Ross, 1965 (Box 34)
    - Kihm, Allen J., 1980 (Box 34)
    - Kilgore, William J., 1963 (Box 34)
    - Kilgour, Frederick G., 1955 (Box 34)
    - Kimura, Motoo, 1982 (Box 34)
      Comments on Neutral Theory of Evolution
    - Kinder Verlag Gmbtt Muchen, 1971-72 (Box 34)
    - King, Donald West, 1969 (Box 34)
    - King, James E., 1978-79 (Box 34)
    - King, Lawrence J., 1975 (Box 34)
    - King, Roma A., Jr., 1958 (Box 34)
    - Kinser, B.M., 1932 (Box 34)
    - Kinsey, Alfred C., 1938 (Box 34)
    - Kinzer, Louis W., 1941 (Box 34)
      Air raid warden
    - Kiriakoff, S.G., 1961 (Box 34)
    - Kirk, S. Raebrien, 1927-28 (Box 34)
    - Kirkman, Rosemary, 1964 (Box 34)
    - Kirkpatrick, Mark, 1981 (Box 34)
    - Kirsch, J.A.W., 1967-71, 73-76, 83 (Box 34)
    - Kitchin, F.L., 1926 (Box 34)
    - Kitchin, William W., 1962-63 (Box 34)
    - Kitts, David B., 1952-53, 57, 60, 63, 70, 77, 82, 84 (Box 34)
      History of geology
    - Klauber, L.M., 1939, 41 (Box 34)
    - Klavins, J.V., 1973 (Box 34)
    - Klein, Randolph S., 1984 (Box 34)
    - Kleipool, R.J.C., 1963 (Box 34)
    - Kline, C.W., 1960 (Box 34)
      Society for the Guidance of Human Evolution
    - Klingener, David, 1970, 79 (Box 34)
    - Klovan, J.E., 1966 (Box 34)
    - Kluwer Book Distributors, 1979 (Box 34)
    - Kmieciah, Kenneth, 1972 (Box 35)
    - Knight, J. Brookes, 1946 (Box 35)
    - Knight, S.H., 1932-33, 36 (Box 35)
    - Knopf, Adolph, 1926, 41, 50 (Box 35)
    - Knopf, Alfred A., Inc., 1953-55, 58-59, 63 (Box 35)
    - Knowlton, Ruth G., 1947 (Box 35)
    - Knox College, 1977 (Box 35)
    - Kochanski, Zdzislaw, 1966 (Box 35)
    - Kochendorfer, Leonard, 1968 (Box 35)
    - Koehler, O., 1963 (Box 35)
    - Koenigswald, G.H.R. von, 1966 (Box 35)
    - Koerner, Harold E., 1935, 46 (Box 35)
    - Kohn, Lawrence A., 1961 (Box 35)
      Darwin and brucellosis
    - Kolb, Kemp Bennett, 1963 (Box 35)
    - Kolchinnsky, E.I., 1981 (Box 35)
    - Koliberyiski, Langin, 1965 (Box 35)
    - Kolker, B., 1960 (Box 35)
    - Konnerth, Andrew, Jr., 1961, 64 (Box 35)
    - Koppelman, Ray, 1961-62 (Box 35)
      College of the Air, WTTV tv
    - Kordus, Norbert, 1974 (Box 35)
    - Kormondy, Edward J., 1957 (Box 35)
    - Kortlandt, Adriaan, 1974-75 (Box 35)
    - Koscielniak, Susan, 1984 (Box 35)
      Columbia Univ. Press Tempo and Mode reprint
    - Koss, Joan D., 1969 (Box 35)
    - Kozub, Robert C., 1974 (Box 35)
      About paleontology as a career
    - Kraatz, Walter C., 1935, 42, 54, 65 (Box 35)
    - Kraglievich, Jorge Lucas, 1956 (Box 35)
    - Krakauer, Daniel, 1974 (Box 35)
    - Kraljevich, Ivy, not dated (Box 35)
    - Kramer, Julia W., 1984 (Box 35)
    - Kranes, Judith E., 1969 (Box 35)
    - Kranz, Peter M., 1978 (Box 35)
    - Kratochvil, J., 1971 (Box 35)
    - Kraus, Michael, 1942 (Box 35)
    - Krause, David W., 1972, 78, 82-83 (Box 35)
      Proposal
    - Kravitz, Ernest, 1973 (Box 35)
    - Krebs, Bernard, 1966 (Box 35)
    - Krehel, Lewis W., 1982 (Box 35)
    - Kreitzer, Dave, 1982 (Box 35)
    - Kring, Walter Donald, 1959 (Box 35)
      Unitarian Church
    - Krishna Murthy Achar, 1970 (Box 35)
    - Krisiloff, Cathy, 1963 (Box 35)
    - Kristiansen, Kristian, 1973 (Box 35)
    - Krogman, Wilton Marion, 1926, 60 (Box 35)
    - Krohn, 1979 (Box 35)
    - Krueger, John R., 1978-79 (Box 35)
    - Kues, Barry S., 1978-79 (Box 35)
      San Juan Basin
    - Kugler, H.G., 1958 (Box 35)
    - Kuhn, Emil (Kuhn-Schnyder), 1951, 54, 59, 61, 68, 71, 76 (Box 35)
      Also under Schnyder, Emil
    - Kuhne, Walter G., 1958-59, 66, 69 (Box 35)
    - Kukla, George J., 1973 (Box 35)
    - Kumamoto, Junji, 1972, 75 (Box 35)
      St. of California curriculum develop: creationism
    - Kumar, Pradeep, 1980 (Box 35)
    - Kumar, Shiv. S., 1974 (Box 35)
    - Kummel, Bernhard, 1971 (Box 35)
    - Kurten, Bjorn, 1955-1982; 61.0 Item(s) (Box 35)
      American Museum of Natural History; Biographical and personal data; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Evolution -- Teeth; Gould, Stephen Jay; Paleontology; Publication -- Science; Recommendations -- Kurten, Bjorn; Research support; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.; Zoology
    - Kurth, G., 1960-61, 65, 68 (Box 35)
    - Kurtz, Paul, 1981 (Box 35)
    - Kurz, Peter, 1974 (Box 35)
      Zephyrus Press, Inc.
    - Kusnezov, Nicholas, 1961 (Box 35)
    - La Bossiere, Jeannine M., 1967 (Box 35)
    - Laboratory of Anthropology, Inc., 1948 (Box 35)
    - Lack, David, 1951, 58, 62 (Box 35)
    - Lacklen, Robert J., 1976 (Box 35)
    - Lacroux, Daniel, 1975 (Box 35)
    - Laird, H.C., 1927 (Box 35)
    - Lal, D., 1980 (Box 35)
    - Lamb, I. Mackenzie, 1959 (Box 35)
    - Lamb, Loretto DeMuth, 1952 (Box 35)
    - Lambrecht, Frank L., 1963, 81 (Box 35)
    - Lambrecht, Kalman, 1929, 32-35 (Box 35)
    - Lammers, George, 1960 (Box 35)
    - Lance, John F., 1964-67, 77, 79 (Box 35)
    - Lance, Katherine (Kitty), 1971, 76-80, 82 (Box 35)
    - Lancini, Abdem Ramon, 1962 (Box 35)
    - Land, George T., 1972 (Box 35)
    - Land, W.G., 1937 (Box 35)
    - Lande, Russell, 1976, 80 (Box 35)
    - Landry, Stuart O., 1967 (Box 35)
    - Lane, Alfred Church, 1936 (Box 35)
    - Lane, H.H., 1941 (Box 35)
    - Langelet, Olof, 1972 (Box 35)
    - Langford, George, 1953 (Box 35)
    - Langston, Wann, Jr., 1972, 74, 76, 81-82 (Box 35)
      SVP
    - Lanham, U.N., 1953 (Box 35)
    - Lanier, Sterling E., 1962-3, 67-70, 72 (Box 35)
    - Lantau, Alfred H., 1965 (Box 35)
    - Lanzavecchia, Giulio, 1976 (Box 35)
      See Lehmann, 1976
    - Laporte, Leo F., 1960-1984; 2 folders (Box 36)
      American Philosophical Society; Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia; Evolution; Gould, Stephen Jay; Harvard University; History of biology, especially genetics; Invitations; Lectures, public speaking; Mayr, Ernst; Osborn, Henry Fairfield; Provine, William B.; Publication -- George Gaylord Simpson Biography; Teaching; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; World War II -- Impact on science; Zoology -- Classification
    - Lara, Mario de, 1964 (Box 36)
    - Larchar, Mary and Arthur W., 1958 (Box 36)
    - Larsen, E., 1936 (Box 36)
    - Larson, Charles, 1957 (Box 36)
    - Lashley, Karl S., 1947 (Box 36)
    - Lasker, Gabriel W., 1946-48, 52, 72 (Box 36)
      American Assoc. of Physical Anthropologists
    - Lasnik, Penelope, 1970 (Box 36)
    - Latchaw, Truly Trousdale, 1977 (Box 36)
    - Latchford, Stephen F., 1947, 53 (Box 36)
      fossils in Argentina, 1700s
    - Lattimore, Owen, 1939, 52, 55, 61 (Box 36)
    - Laub, Richard J., 1960-61, 81 (Box 36)
      field of paleontology
    - Lauffer, Max A., 1977 (Box 36)
    - Laurent, Abbe Goulven, 1964 (Box 36)
    - Laurent, Raymond F., 1964-66, 69-70, 72, 75-83 (Box 36)
    - Lavigne, Robert J., 1961 (Box 36)
    - Lavocat, Abbe Rene J.M., 1947-48, 52, 56-57, 62-65, 71, 73-76, 81 (Box 36)
    - Lavoie, Joseph C., 1947 (Box 36)
    - Law, M. Eprevel, 1968 (Box 36)
    - Lawrence University, 1959, 64 (Box 36)
    - Lawrence, Barbara, 1960, 71 (Box 36)
    - Lawrence, John F., 1967 (Box 36)
    - Lawrence, Seymour, Inc., 1968 (Box 36)
    - Lay, Douglas M., 1968 (Box 36)
    - Le Faivre, Carole N., 1978 (Box 36)
    - LeVene, Clara M., 1937 (Box 36)
    - LeVene, Clara Mae, 1934 (Box 36)
    - Leakey, Louis S. B. (Louis Seymour Bazett), 1958-1981; 2 folders (Box 36)
      2 folders: #1:58-62 #2:63-69, 81
      Conferences and symposia; Evolution; Evolution -- Teeth; Hooijer, Dirk Albert; Lectures, public speaking; National Research Council; National Science Foundation; Paleontology -- Africa; Patterson, Bryan; Photographs; Publication; Recommendations; Referee's report; Research support; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.; Zoology -- Africa
    - Leakey, Richard E., 1972, 80, 82 (Box 36)
    - Lean, Martin E., 1962 (Box 36)
    - Leanza, Armando F., 1954 (Box 36)
    - Lear, Norman, 1982 (Box 36)
    - Leatherman, E.W., 1968 (Box 36)
      Cosmology/ethics
    - Leclereq, Jean, 1957, 60, 67 (Box 36)
    - Lecompte, M., 1964 (Box 36)
    - Lednardi, Piero, 1971 (Box 36)